Do a relaxing.
Two wheels on each side.
You can carry two lights.
You know, you love that thing down.
That's all.
These are also on the next side.
It's just a bit tight.
It's six.
It's settled down in the countryside.
It's only real light.
You think so?
No.
It's good.
It's going to be kind of hard to do.
But you can take minutes now.
We've been talking about that three minutes.
You know what I mean?
You can carry one.
It's just a bit.
It's a bit.
You can carry one.
Yeah, he's all-worked.
He's big.
A lot of things.
I don't know if that's what I mean.
I mean it was just a hand that's what I mean.
It's all about how.
It's just like I got a thing.
You know what I mean?
So, regular meeting of the Miami Special Utility Authority for today's date, I don't know
or two, it's indication by the pastor of First Baptist Church Rick Longpot, Rick
Thanks for being here.
Thank you.
Let's pray to get it.
Finally, it's always such an honor to come and lift up our city leaders and the decisions that
they make.
Father, we all know these are very crucial times in the life of our nation and so we just
just even as our community, we pray for wisdom and Father, we just want our community
to be great and just pray that our leaders just give them wisdom to make the decisions
that they need to make tonight and Father, would you just continue to bless us and bless
our community in Jesus name?
Amen.
Please join me in the pledge.
I don't remember if we were to come up with a pledge to the United States or America and to
the Republic for which it stands, one nation behind the end of the Gospel, with a good
opportunity to ask us for our honor.
I don't remember if we were to come up with a can put down the scheduled portion of our characters
as anyone in the audience, it was to address the authority.
Item 5 is consenting.
The staff is recommending item 6 through 9 for the consenting agenda, there are no questions
of the entertainer motion, my own mic Emotion that proved item 6 through 9 and consent
of agenda.
And the second.
I'll second it.
O call please.
Johnson.
Lewis?
I.
Weston.
Forster.
I.
Adam Tames.
Be a business in any business need?
No, you're on it.
11 is staff of boards, or fortune in your pocket if they're in question for staff.
That's it.
Troules, trustee and community announcements, so we have any announcements.
Item 13 is adjournment.
Do we have a motion to adjourn?
Motion adjourn.
Second.
I'll second that.
We'll call please.
Weston.
All right.
Show.
See you.
I'm sorry.